openlaszlo.org 2013-03-31

# Privacy Policy | OpenLaszlo

**Laszlo Systems, Inc.** respects your right to privacy and your right to  
limit information exchanges to those initiated by you. Your trust is very important  
to us, as well as your confidence. Please review this Privacy Policy to better  
understand the kinds of information we collect about you and other visitors  
to the Laszlo Web site as part of our business. We encourage you to send us  
questions, comments, or suggestions about our policy to [privacy@laszlosystems.com](mailto:privacy@laszlosystems.com).

**When Laszlo collects personal information**  
Laszlo gathers information from you and other users of the Laszlo Web site in three ways: voluntary registration, log files, or 'cookie' technology, and IP/URL addresses.

  * **Voluntary Registration.** When you register with Laszlo on the Laszlo Web site, we ask for certain personal information. We also sometimes ask that you register certain personal information with third parties when we conduct marketing surveys through those third parties.
  * **Cookies.** The Laszlo Web site automatically uses log files or 'cookies' to store and track your preferences to provide you with a more personalized Web site and to provide you with access to password-protected areas of the Laszlo Web site when you are authorized to do so by Laszlo. Once you enter the Laszlo Web site, a cookie follows you through your click stream path. Laszlo also collects information regarding the pages, links, banners, icons and other parts of the Laszlo Web site that are accessed or clicked on during a visit to the Laszlo Web site, including information regarding the date, time and duration of the visit.
  * **IP Address/URL.** Laszlo also logs IP addresses of you and other users of the Laszlo Web site for the purposes of systems administration and to collect and report information in aggregate form.

**How is my personally identifiable information used?**

  * **Customized Look and Feel.** As noted above, Laszlo may gather and use your information in order to provide you with an improved and customized look and feel.
  * **Aggregate Information.** Laszlo also gathers your information for the purpose of reviewing demographics, traffic patterns, and other information in the aggregate for internal business and marketing purposes as well as to better understand what users are seeking and learning at the Laszlo Web site.
  * **E-mail.** If you register with the Laszlo Web site and indicate that you would like to receive additional information from us, Laszlo may email you with informative messages about products and services we believe may be of interest to you. As a member of our Laszlo community, we want you to be able to choose whether you wish to receive additional information from us regarding products and services. That is why we ask you upon registration whether you wish to be contacted regarding Laszlo news, upcoming products and services.

**How can I stop receiving mail from Laszlo?**  
If you are receiving e-mail from us and no longer wish to do so, please send  
us an e-mail request to be removed from our e-mail list at [webmaster@laszlosystems.com](mailto:webmaster@laszlosystems.com).

**Who does Laszlo share information with?**  
Laszlo discloses your information as part of aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to partners and other third parties. However aggregate data does not disclose your personally identifiable information. We will not disclose your personally identifiable information to any third party except (i) to provide you with activities, services or products requested by you, including, without limitation, enrollment by you in contests or promotions; (ii) with your consent; or (iii) as we are required by law or regulation where we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with law or legal process, to protect or defend our rights or property, or to defend against fraud. In addition, we may disclose your personally identifiable information in connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or most of the assets of Laszlo to another entity.

**What else should I know about my privacy?**  
You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personal information online in a public area, such as a chat room or on an e-mail discussion list, that information may be collected and used by others. We do not control the actions of our visitors and registered users. If you disclose personal information in a publicly accessible place in the Laszlo Web site, you do so at your own risk and you understand that your submitted information may be collected and used by others to send you unsolicited messages, advertisements, or for other purposes. Laszlo does not control the privacy policies of third party Laszlo Web sites to which we provide links. Please be aware that if you click on an advertisement or third party link, you will be subject to the third partyís privacy policy.

Please remember that you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any password you use to register and you should always be careful and responsible whenever disclosing information online.

Although Laszlo uses reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your personal information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Laszlo assumes no liability for disclosure of data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized third parties.

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**  
By using the Laszlo Web site and any products and services from the Laszlo Web site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. You agree that Laszlo may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Laszlo Web site. You may review our Privacy Policy at any time by visiting the Laszlo Web site. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine whether the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of the Laszlo Web site or products and services from the Laszlo Web site following the posting of the revised policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

**Laszlo Would Like to Receive Your Comments**  
We are committed to maintaining your trust in the Internet, and in Laszlo.  
Please let us know if you have any suggestions about how we can improve our  
privacy policy or if you have additional questions regarding our collection  
and/or use of personal information.

You may contact us by email at: [privacy@laszlosystems.com](mailto:privacy@laszlosystems.com)

Or contact us by mail at:

**Attention: Privacy Policy  
Laszlo Systems, Inc.  
2600 Campus Drive  
San Mateo, CA, 94403**
